# BENJAMIN SOLT

FULL STACK ENGINEER

### **SUMMARY**

Web Developer with experience in coding, email marketing, API's, and game app development.

Prior experience in freelance art and 3D art and animation.

Self taught Epic Game's Unreal Engine.

Customer service professional with 10 years of experience.

#### **SKILLS**

- WordPress
- CSS
- HTMI
- React
- Dependable

- Redux

- JavaScript
- Adobe Creative Suite
- GitHub
- Firebase
- Unreal Engine
- 3D Studio Max Empathetic
  - Service Oriented

## **EDUCATION**

## **BLOOMTECH - (FORMERLY LAMBDA)**

August 2020

Full Stack Engineer

- HTLM, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux
- Jest, Python, GitHub, Node.js

#### **TEMPLE UNIVERSITY**

May 2012

- Intensive certificate course for creative web design
- Created page layouts and art assets
- Utilized HTML, CSS and Dreamweaver

## THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

December 2007

• Bachelor of Science Degree in Media Arts and Animation

## **CONTACT INFO**

- Bensolt@gmail.com
- Cell: 215 360 5410
- Fort Washington, PA
- Bensolt.com
- Github
- LinkedIn

## RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

#### **INERTIA MARKETING - DIGITAL PRODUCTION**

MAY 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

- Created websites/landing pages for clients using WordPress
- Developed HTML email marketing promotions
- Built game app with JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Firebase

#### **METRO ESPORTS - STEM INSTRUCTOR**

OCTOBER 2021 - JUNE 2022

• Taught introductory programming classes with JavaScript in person and remote

#### **GROA - FRONT END DEVELOPER**

FEBRUARY 2020 - APRIL 2020

App to recommend movies based on user's prior movie ratings with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, AWS

- As Front End Developer built authorization, login, and display layout of movie page
- Solved problems and trouble shot bugs with team members
- Collaborated remotely with team of 6 web developers, 2 data scientists, and 1 UX designer

#### LOGO AND ART ASSET DESIGNER

NOVEMBER 2013 - NOVEMBER 2017

- Created logos and t-shirt graphics to meet company's needs
- Animated, modeled and textured 3D art assets
- Built 3D rotating model of a medical device

## PERSONAL PORTFOLIO (BENSOLT.COM) APRIL 2020 - 2022

 Designed, developed and implemented React based site to display a diverse range of personal projects using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React